gatewayedi.com 2017-12-20

# Privacy Policy | TriZetto

TriZetto.com (the "Web Site") is owned and operated by TriZetto Corporation. Our privacy policy explains how we may collect, use and aggregate personal information about you when you visit this Web Site. This privacy policy solely relates to this website; TriZetto has adopted separate privacy policies with respect to its offline operations.

#### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Web Site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of TriZetto's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Web Site and exit the Web Site immediately. Your continued use of TriZetto's Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

#### Uses of Information Submitted and Collected

During your use of the Web Site we will collect certain information from you. For each visitor to the Web Site, TriZetto's servers automatically collect information about which pages you visit and your IP address or domain name. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to more efficiently administer our Web Site and to gather broad demographic information.

In consideration for the use of the Web Site, you agree that the information you provide will be true, accurate, current, and complete and that you will maintain and update that information. Failure to do so will give TriZetto the right to suspend or terminate your use of the Web Site. TriZetto will not sell your personally-identifying information (your email address and any contact information you provide), but reserves the right to share certain demographic and profile data with business partners solely on an aggregated basis.

TriZetto will disclose your personally-identifying information only in special cases, such as (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (ii) when TriZetto has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to TriZetto.com users or other persons or violating the Terms and Conditions of Use for this Web Site.

#### Cookies

TriZetto may place a "cookie" on the browser of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. The cookie itself does not contain any personally-identifying information, but may be used to tell when your computer has contacted TriZetto.com. TriZetto uses the information for editorial purposes and to customize delivery of information specific to your interests.

#### Links

This Web Site contains hyperlinks to other sites. TriZetto is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with TriZetto. The linked sites may collect personal information from you when you link to their site. This collecting of information is not subject to TriZetto's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you visit by linking from our Web Site.

#### Security

The Web Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Notification of Changes

This Privacy Policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web Site or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use TriZetto.com, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.

#### Contacting Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact TriZetto at:

TriZetto Corporation  
Corporate Headquarters  
9655 Maroon Circle  
Englewood, CO 80112  
attn: Legal Department

phone: (800) 569-1222
